Jake Williams

Runner

+44 (0) 7505 555 717 <u>jake@jpwfilm.co.uk</u> <u>https://jpwfilm.co.uk</u>

SKILLS

I have experience and training on a wide range of cameras, lighting and grip equipment, additionally I'm familiar with **Adobe Creative Suite** including, but not limited to, **Premiere Pro**, **Photoshop**, and **Audition**. I'm a hard worker with a wide range of experience in many different areas, which helped me develop my **leadership**, **problem solving**, **team working**, and **time management** skills.

INDUSTRY EXPERIENCE

Freelance /

Corporate & Event Filming

SEPTEMBER 2018 - PRESENT

I ensure the clients' brief is met with a creative and professional piece of work. In the past I've worked with theatre companies, corporations, and universities. I adapted my working style for each client to be as efficient as possible while maintaining quality.

Event Manager; Filmmaker Liaison /

Winchester Film Festival

2018 & 2019, WINCHESTER

During my time volunteering for the festival, I successfully organised an awards ceremony and a filmmaker's social, along with nightly film screenings. Under time pressures, I had to manage myself in order to deliver my assistance to the founder, oversee student teams, and complete my own tasks.

1st AD and more /

Student Films

SEPTEMBER 2017 - MAY 2020, WINCHESTER

I've performed rudimentary roles on student film sets and I'm ready to take them to the next level. These include: 1st AD, Script Supervisor, Producer, Writer, and Runner. In each case I had to learn on the job and worked tirelessly to deliver in the role.

Production Coordinator /

'Downtime'

2018, WINCHESTER

A co-creation project between students and lectures, I oversaw the communication between the departments, attended location recces to assist department heads, and worked on set as a **3rd AD** and **Runner**.

NON-INDUSTRY EXPERIENCE

Nanny

APRIL 2018 - MAY 2020

Senior Travel Trainer / Norfolk County Council

2017 - 2019

EDUCATION

BA (Hons) Film Production /

University of Winchester

2017 - 2020

Recent graduate with a predicted result of 2:1.

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Helper | Hampshire Pride (2019) **Scout Troop Assistant** (2013–2020)

PAST EMPLOYERS

University of Winchester Winchester Poetry Festival Winchester Theatre Royal